profootballweekly.com 2010-06-20

# ProFootballWeekly.com

_Updated April 5, 2009_

Your personal privacy is important to us at ProFootballWeekly.com. The information that we gather and how it is used is described below. This policy applies only to Pro Football Weekly. Be sure to check the privacy policies of any sites that advertise with us as they may differ from our privacy policy.

**About IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet. This address is used to serve the pages that you request to your computer. IP addresses are used by us to count unique visitors, to diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. They are also used to report anonymous aggregate information to third parties. Your IP address is not connected to your personal information and so, when we use IP-related data, we are looking at a logged user session but we do not know who you are.

**About Cookies**

Cookies are used by many sites including ProFootballWeekly.com to customize your experience on the site. To do this, bits of information called cookies are placed on your computer's hard drive for tracking purposes. You may disable cookies on your computer; however if you do so, you may not be able to use certain features of our site.

**Anonymous Aggregate Information**

As part of the tracking process, ProFootballWeekly.com will collect anonymous aggregate information and may share it with advertisers and affiliates for the purpose of providing the most beneficial content possible to our visitors. This information includes such items as the number of visitors to the site, access times, referring web site addresses and demographic information (such as age, gender, etc.), all of an anonymous nature.

**Personal Information**

There are many things that can be done on our site without providing any personal information to us at all. There are also instances where we may offer you the opportunity to register for premium services, complete a survey online or to enter a contest or a sweepstakes. In these situations, we may ask you to provide personal information such as email address, full name, street address, telephone number, hobbies, and preferences. This information will be used to contact you or for internal purposes and will not be shared with any party outside of Pro Football Weekly.

We also may use personal information to display custom, personalized content to our visitors or to send newsletters, emails, promotional materials and other updates on a periodic basis. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information.

**Data collection of non-personally identifying information**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Links to Other Sites**

ProFootballWeekly.com may offer links to other sites so that you can conveniently visit these sites. However, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of these sites and recommend that you review and understand the privacy statement of each site that you are on.

**Security**

Security of your personal information is very important to us. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt important information such as your credit card information in order to prevent unauthorized access. We incorporate standard industry practices internally and with our service providers to maintain the security of your personal information.

**Children's privacy**

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) in the United States does not allow the collection of any personal information from anyone under the age of 13 who resides in the United States. Therefore, children under 13 should not submit any information about themselves via forms. We will not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you submit such personal information, you warrant that you are over the age of 13 and are not subject to COPPA.

**Your agreement**

Your use of this web site constitutes your express consent to the collection and use of information as described in this privacy statement. This privacy statement is subject to change. Any material change in the manner in which we handle personally identifiable information will be prominently posted prior to implementing the change. Your continued use of the site more than 30 days following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

**Contact information:**

This site is operated by:

Pro Football Weekly LLC  
302 Saunders Road, Suite 100  
Riverwoods IL  60015  
(847) 940-1100

Inquiries about this policy can be directed to [pfwmail@pfwmedia.com](mailto:pfwmedia.com?subject=Privacy%20statement).
